Hi Friends, hope you all are doing good
Today, In this video, I will give you details,
regarding Religare Care plan, and later in this video,
I will also talk about special features and benefits of this plan.
This video is going to be very beneficial for you
so guys please watch this video till the end
So, before starting the video,
I would like to thank all my viewers,
who keep supporting us and who liked our videos
and those who have already subscribed to my channel.
And if you have not yet subscribed to my channel,
then please subscribe to my channel, like my video
and press the bell icon.
This will help you to stay updated with my latest videos.
And if you are watching my video first time,
then welcome to my Channel, I am your health consultant kajal.
let's start
Friends Religare has bring a Care plan, For a worry free
today and tomorrow.
Apart from it, In addition to hassle free claims,
Religare also provides you a facility of direct claims settlement.
Religare ensure you have access to the best healthcare services,
that's why Religare Care gives you the freedom of choosing
certain listed treatment in India or Abroad.
First, I will talk about some basic covers of this plan.
This plan provides you the benefits of an Accidental emergency
cover from Day 1.
Coverage for Advanced Technologies like robotics surgery,
stem cell therapy or Bornchical thermoplasty is available in this plan
Coverage for Modern Treatment like oral chemotherapy,
bariatic surgery or intra vitreal injections are available in this plan
you also get the facility of pre and post hospitalization.
It means before you get hospitalized there are few expenses,
which you get in your pre medical home treatment
this plan also covers those expenses upto 30 days.